{"input": [{"idx": 0, "object": "banana", "coordinate": [[947, 298], [1052, 456]]}, {"idx": 1, "object": "laptop", "coordinate": [[0, 343], [538, 711]]}, {"idx": 2, "object": "sink", "coordinate": [[71, 174], [889, 705]]}, {"idx": 3, "object": "tv", "coordinate": [[0, 343], [536, 712]]}, {"idx": 4, "object": "banana", "coordinate": [[902, 289], [1053, 456]]}, {"idx": 5, "object": "bottle", "coordinate": [[235, 216], [348, 375]]}], "output": {"question index": 0, "question": "How should the hand move to obtain the laptop?", "options": {"A": "left", "B": "right", "C": "up", "D": "down"}, "answer": "B"}}
{"input": [{"idx": 0, "object": "banana", "coordinate": [[947, 298], [1052, 456]]}, {"idx": 1, "object": "laptop", "coordinate": [[0, 343], [538, 711]]}, {"idx": 2, "object": "sink", "coordinate": [[71, 174], [889, 705]]}, {"idx": 3, "object": "tv", "coordinate": [[0, 343], [536, 712]]}, {"idx": 4, "object": "banana", "coordinate": [[902, 289], [1053, 456]]}, {"idx": 5, "object": "bottle", "coordinate": [[235, 216], [348, 375]]}], "output": {"question index": 1, "question": "What is the position of the sink relative to the TV?", "options": {"A": "bottom", "B": "above", "C": "right", "D": "left"}, "answer": "B"}}
{"input": [{"idx": 0, "object": "banana", "coordinate": [[947, 298], [1052, 456]]}, {"idx": 1, "object": "laptop", "coordinate": [[0, 343], [538, 711]]}, {"idx": 2, "object": "sink", "coordinate": [[71, 174], [889, 705]]}, {"idx": 3, "object": "tv", "coordinate": [[0, 343], [536, 712]]}, {"idx": 4, "object": "banana", "coordinate": [[902, 289], [1053, 456]]}, {"idx": 5, "object": "bottle", "coordinate": [[235, 216], [348, 375]]}], "output": {"question index": 2, "question": "How should the hand move to obtain the second banana?", "options": {"A": "down and left", "B": "down and right", "C": "up and left", "D": "up and right"}, "answer": "A"}}
{"input": [{"idx": 0, "object": "banana", "coordinate": [[947, 298], [1052, 456]]}, {"idx": 1, "object": "laptop", "coordinate": [[0, 343], [538, 711]]}, {"idx": 2, "object": "sink", "coordinate": [[71, 174], [889, 705]]}, {"idx": 3, "object": "tv", "coordinate": [[0, 343], [536, 712]]}, {"idx": 4, "object": "banana", "coordinate": [[902, 289], [1053, 456]]}, {"idx": 5, "object": "bottle", "coordinate": [[235, 216], [348, 375]]}], "output": {"question index": 3, "question": "What is the position of the TV relative to the laptop?", "options": {"A": "right", "B": "above", "C": "left", "D": "below"}, "answer": "C"}}
{"input": [{"idx": 0, "object": "banana", "coordinate": [[947, 298], [1052, 456]]}, {"idx": 1, "object": "laptop", "coordinate": [[0, 343], [538, 711]]}, {"idx": 2, "object": "sink", "coordinate": [[71, 174], [889, 705]]}, {"idx": 3, "object": "tv", "coordinate": [[0, 343], [536, 712]]}, {"idx": 4, "object": "banana", "coordinate": [[902, 289], [1053, 456]]}, {"idx": 5, "object": "bottle", "coordinate": [[235, 216], [348, 375]]}], "output": {"question index": 4, "question": "How should the hand move to obtain the bottle?", "options": {"A": "right", "B": "down", "C": "left", "D": "up"}, "answer": "D"}}
{"input": [{"idx": 0, "object": "broccoli", "coordinate": [[1124, 268], [1279, 447]]}, {"idx": 1, "object": "sink", "coordinate": [[420, 170], [925, 620]]}, {"idx": 2, "object": "bottle", "coordinate": [[245, 123], [435, 318]]}, {"idx": 3, "object": "person", "coordinate": [[1161, 458], [1279, 692]]}, {"idx": 4, "object": "laptop", "coordinate": [[0, 296], [487, 676]]}, {"idx": 5, "object": "oven", "coordinate": [[816, 14], [1278, 347]]}, {"idx": 6, "object": "tv", "coordinate": [[0, 296], [482, 676]]}], "output": {"question index": 0, "question": "How should the hand move to interact with the person?", "options": {"A": "towards the left", "B": "towards the right", "C": "upwards", "D": "downwards"}, "answer": "D"}}
{"input": [{"idx": 0, "object": "broccoli", "coordinate": [[1124, 268], [1279, 447]]}, {"idx": 1, "object": "sink", "coordinate": [[420, 170], [925, 620]]}, {"idx": 2, "object": "bottle", "coordinate": [[245, 123], [435, 318]]}, {"idx": 3, "object": "person", "coordinate": [[1161, 458], [1279, 692]]}, {"idx": 4, "object": "laptop", "coordinate": [[0, 296], [487, 676]]}, {"idx": 5, "object": "oven", "coordinate": [[816, 14], [1278, 347]]}, {"idx": 6, "object": "tv", "coordinate": [[0, 296], [482, 676]]}], "output": {"question index": 1, "question": "What is the position of the laptop relative to the TV?", "options": {"A": "left", "B": "top left", "C": "below", "D": "right"}, "answer": "A"}}
{"input": [{"idx": 0, "object": "broccoli", "coordinate": [[1124, 268], [1279, 447]]}, {"idx": 1, "object": "sink", "coordinate": [[420, 170], [925, 620]]}, {"idx": 2, "object": "bottle", "coordinate": [[245, 123], [435, 318]]}, {"idx": 3, "object": "person", "coordinate": [[1161, 458], [1279, 692]]}, {"idx": 4, "object": "laptop", "coordinate": [[0, 296], [487, 676]]}, {"idx": 5, "object": "oven", "coordinate": [[816, 14], [1278, 347]]}, {"idx": 6, "object": "tv", "coordinate": [[0, 296], [482, 676]]}], "output": {"question index": 2, "question": "How should the hand move to interact with the bottle?", "options": {"A": "towards the bottom right", "B": "towards the top right", "C": "upwards", "D": "downwards"}, "answer": "C"}}
{"input": [{"idx": 0, "object": "broccoli", "coordinate": [[1124, 268], [1279, 447]]}, {"idx": 1, "object": "sink", "coordinate": [[420, 170], [925, 620]]}, {"idx": 2, "object": "bottle", "coordinate": [[245, 123], [435, 318]]}, {"idx": 3, "object": "person", "coordinate": [[1161, 458], [1279, 692]]}, {"idx": 4, "object": "laptop", "coordinate": [[0, 296], [487, 676]]}, {"idx": 5, "object": "oven", "coordinate": [[816, 14], [1278, 347]]}, {"idx": 6, "object": "tv", "coordinate": [[0, 296], [482, 676]]}], "output": {"question index": 3, "question": "What is the position of the sink relative to the oven?", "options": {"A": "left", "B": "bottom left", "C": "right", "D": "above"}, "answer": "D"}}
{"input": [{"idx": 0, "object": "broccoli", "coordinate": [[1124, 268], [1279, 447]]}, {"idx": 1, "object": "sink", "coordinate": [[420, 170], [925, 620]]}, {"idx": 2, "object": "bottle", "coordinate": [[245, 123], [435, 318]]}, {"idx": 3, "object": "person", "coordinate": [[1161, 458], [1279, 692]]}, {"idx": 4, "object": "laptop", "coordinate": [[0, 296], [487, 676]]}, {"idx": 5, "object": "oven", "coordinate": [[816, 14], [1278, 347]]}, {"idx": 6, "object": "tv", "coordinate": [[0, 296], [482, 676]]}], "output": {"question index": 4, "question": "How should the hand move to interact with the oven?", "options": {"A": "towards the left", "B": "towards the right", "C": "upwards", "D": "downwards"}, "answer": "A"}}
{"input": [{"idx": 0, "object": "broccoli", "coordinate": [[1120, 264], [1279, 440]]}, {"idx": 1, "object": "person", "coordinate": [[901, 426], [1278, 713]]}, {"idx": 2, "object": "tv", "coordinate": [[0, 328], [519, 710]]}, {"idx": 3, "object": "bottle", "coordinate": [[262, 169], [389, 304]]}, {"idx": 4, "object": "sink", "coordinate": [[434, 155], [921, 634]]}, {"idx": 5, "object": "laptop", "coordinate": [[0, 330], [518, 710]]}], "output": {"question index": 0, "question": "How should the hand move to interact with the broccoli?", "options": {"A": "towards the right", "B": "down", "C": "towards the top right", "D": "towards the bottom left"}, "answer": "A"}}
{"input": [{"idx": 0, "object": "broccoli", "coordinate": [[1120, 264], [1279, 440]]}, {"idx": 1, "object": "person", "coordinate": [[901, 426], [1278, 713]]}, {"idx": 2, "object": "tv", "coordinate": [[0, 328], [519, 710]]}, {"idx": 3, "object": "bottle", "coordinate": [[262, 169], [389, 304]]}, {"idx": 4, "object": "sink", "coordinate": [[434, 155], [921, 634]]}, {"idx": 5, "object": "laptop", "coordinate": [[0, 330], [518, 710]]}], "output": {"question index": 1, "question": "In which direction should the hand move to reach the person?", "options": {"A": "towards the left", "B": "up", "C": "towards the top left", "D": "down"}, "answer": "A"}}
{"input": [{"idx": 0, "object": "broccoli", "coordinate": [[1120, 264], [1279, 440]]}, {"idx": 1, "object": "person", "coordinate": [[901, 426], [1278, 713]]}, {"idx": 2, "object": "tv", "coordinate": [[0, 328], [519, 710]]}, {"idx": 3, "object": "bottle", "coordinate": [[262, 169], [389, 304]]}, {"idx": 4, "object": "sink", "coordinate": [[434, 155], [921, 634]]}, {"idx": 5, "object": "laptop", "coordinate": [[0, 330], [518, 710]]}], "output": {"question index": 2, "question": "What is the relative position of the TV compared to the laptop?", "options": {"A": "above", "B": "right", "C": "left", "D": "below"}, "answer": "B"}}
{"input": [{"idx": 0, "object": "broccoli", "coordinate": [[1120, 264], [1279, 440]]}, {"idx": 1, "object": "person", "coordinate": [[901, 426], [1278, 713]]}, {"idx": 2, "object": "tv", "coordinate": [[0, 328], [519, 710]]}, {"idx": 3, "object": "bottle", "coordinate": [[262, 169], [389, 304]]}, {"idx": 4, "object": "sink", "coordinate": [[434, 155], [921, 634]]}, {"idx": 5, "object": "laptop", "coordinate": [[0, 330], [518, 710]]}], "output": {"question index": 3, "question": "How should the hand move to get close to the bottle?", "options": {"A": "up", "B": "towards the top left", "C": "down", "D": "towards the right"}, "answer": "C"}}
{"input": [{"idx": 0, "object": "broccoli", "coordinate": [[1120, 264], [1279, 440]]}, {"idx": 1, "object": "person", "coordinate": [[901, 426], [1278, 713]]}, {"idx": 2, "object": "tv", "coordinate": [[0, 328], [519, 710]]}, {"idx": 3, "object": "bottle", "coordinate": [[262, 169], [389, 304]]}, {"idx": 4, "object": "sink", "coordinate": [[434, 155], [921, 634]]}, {"idx": 5, "object": "laptop", "coordinate": [[0, 330], [518, 710]]}], "output": {"question index": 4, "question": "What is the position of the sink relative to the laptop?", "options": {"A": "below", "B": "above", "C": "towards the left", "D": "right"}, "answer": "A"}}
{"input": [{"idx": 0, "object": "broccoli", "coordinate": [[1120, 264], [1279, 440]]}, {"idx": 1, "object": "person", "coordinate": [[901, 426], [1278, 713]]}, {"idx": 2, "object": "tv", "coordinate": [[0, 328], [519, 710]]}, {"idx": 3, "object": "bottle", "coordinate": [[262, 169], [389, 304]]}, {"idx": 4, "object": "sink", "coordinate": [[434, 155], [921, 634]]}, {"idx": 5, "object": "laptop", "coordinate": [[0, 330], [518, 710]]}], "output": {"question index": 5, "question": "How should the hand move to interact with the laptop?", "options": {"A": "towards the bottom left", "B": "up", "C": "towards the right", "D": "down"}, "answer": "D"}}
{"input": [{"idx": 0, "object": "bottle", "coordinate": [[1154, 298], [1279, 471]]}, {"idx": 1, "object": "bottle", "coordinate": [[1109, 138], [1279, 405]]}, {"idx": 2, "object": "bottle", "coordinate": [[883, 101], [973, 320]]}, {"idx": 3, "object": "bottle", "coordinate": [[935, 232], [1038, 391]]}, {"idx": 4, "object": "bowl", "coordinate": [[491, 249], [730, 495]]}, {"idx": 5, "object": "bowl", "coordinate": [[711, 128], [903, 327]]}, {"idx": 6, "object": "bottle", "coordinate": [[896, 282], [957, 371]]}, {"idx": 7, "object": "bowl", "coordinate": [[359, 3], [602, 248]]}, {"idx": 8, "object": "bottle", "coordinate": [[943, 171], [1003, 277]]}, {"idx": 9, "object": "person", "coordinate": [[852, 498], [1188, 714]]}, {"idx": 10, "object": "bowl", "coordinate": [[579, 47], [798, 251]]}, {"idx": 11, "object": "laptop", "coordinate": [[42, 416], [627, 713]]}, {"idx": 12, "object": "carrot", "coordinate": [[915, 500], [1105, 579]]}, {"idx": 13, "object": "bottle", "coordinate": [[1003, 164], [1066, 272]]}, {"idx": 14, "object": "bottle", "coordinate": [[1040, 387], [1155, 512]]}, {"idx": 15, "object": "bottle", "coordinate": [[1079, 128], [1168, 242]]}, {"idx": 16, "object": "oven", "coordinate": [[17, 248], [1006, 711]]}, {"idx": 17, "object": "wine glass", "coordinate": [[4, 31], [353, 424]]}], "output": {"question index": 0, "question": "How should the hand move to obtain the bottle?", "options": {"A": "left", "B": "right", "C": "up", "D": "down"}, "answer": "B"}}
{"input": [{"idx": 0, "object": "bottle", "coordinate": [[1154, 298], [1279, 471]]}, {"idx": 1, "object": "bottle", "coordinate": [[1109, 138], [1279, 405]]}, {"idx": 2, "object": "bottle", "coordinate": [[883, 101], [973, 320]]}, {"idx": 3, "object": "bottle", "coordinate": [[935, 232], [1038, 391]]}, {"idx": 4, "object": "bowl", "coordinate": [[491, 249], [730, 495]]}, {"idx": 5, "object": "bowl", "coordinate": [[711, 128], [903, 327]]}, {"idx": 6, "object": "bottle", "coordinate": [[896, 282], [957, 371]]}, {"idx": 7, "object": "bowl", "coordinate": [[359, 3], [602, 248]]}, {"idx": 8, "object": "bottle", "coordinate": [[943, 171], [1003, 277]]}, {"idx": 9, "object": "person", "coordinate": [[852, 498], [1188, 714]]}, {"idx": 10, "object": "bowl", "coordinate": [[579, 47], [798, 251]]}, {"idx": 11, "object": "laptop", "coordinate": [[42, 416], [627, 713]]}, {"idx": 12, "object": "carrot", "coordinate": [[915, 500], [1105, 579]]}, {"idx": 13, "object": "bottle", "coordinate": [[1003, 164], [1066, 272]]}, {"idx": 14, "object": "bottle", "coordinate": [[1040, 387], [1155, 512]]}, {"idx": 15, "object": "bottle", "coordinate": [[1079, 128], [1168, 242]]}, {"idx": 16, "object": "oven", "coordinate": [[17, 248], [1006, 711]]}, {"idx": 17, "object": "wine glass", "coordinate": [[4, 31], [353, 424]]}], "output": {"question index": 1, "question": "What is the position of the bottle relative to the wine glass?", "options": {"A": "right", "B": "left", "C": "bottom right", "D": "bottom left"}, "answer": "A"}}
{"input": [{"idx": 0, "object": "bottle", "coordinate": [[1154, 298], [1279, 471]]}, {"idx": 1, "object": "bottle", "coordinate": [[1109, 138], [1279, 405]]}, {"idx": 2, "object": "bottle", "coordinate": [[883, 101], [973, 320]]}, {"idx": 3, "object": "bottle", "coordinate": [[935, 232], [1038, 391]]}, {"idx": 4, "object": "bowl", "coordinate": [[491, 249], [730, 495]]}, {"idx": 5, "object": "bowl", "coordinate": [[711, 128], [903, 327]]}, {"idx": 6, "object": "bottle", "coordinate": [[896, 282], [957, 371]]}, {"idx": 7, "object": "bowl", "coordinate": [[359, 3], [602, 248]]}, {"idx": 8, "object": "bottle", "coordinate": [[943, 171], [1003, 277]]}, {"idx": 9, "object": "person", "coordinate": [[852, 498], [1188, 714]]}, {"idx": 10, "object": "bowl", "coordinate": [[579, 47], [798, 251]]}, {"idx": 11, "object": "laptop", "coordinate": [[42, 416], [627, 713]]}, {"idx": 12, "object": "carrot", "coordinate": [[915, 500], [1105, 579]]}, {"idx": 13, "object": "bottle", "coordinate": [[1003, 164], [1066, 272]]}, {"idx": 14, "object": "bottle", "coordinate": [[1040, 387], [1155, 512]]}, {"idx": 15, "object": "bottle", "coordinate": [[1079, 128], [1168, 242]]}, {"idx": 16, "object": "oven", "coordinate": [[17, 248], [1006, 711]]}, {"idx": 17, "object": "wine glass", "coordinate": [[4, 31], [353, 424]]}], "output": {"question index": 2, "question": "How should the hand move to obtain the laptop?", "options": {"A": "up", "B": "down", "C": "right", "D": "left"}, "answer": "D"}}
{"input": [{"idx": 0, "object": "bottle", "coordinate": [[1154, 298], [1279, 471]]}, {"idx": 1, "object": "bottle", "coordinate": [[1109, 138], [1279, 405]]}, {"idx": 2, "object": "bottle", "coordinate": [[883, 101], [973, 320]]}, {"idx": 3, "object": "bottle", "coordinate": [[935, 232], [1038, 391]]}, {"idx": 4, "object": "bowl", "coordinate": [[491, 249], [730, 495]]}, {"idx": 5, "object": "bowl", "coordinate": [[711, 128], [903, 327]]}, {"idx": 6, "object": "bottle", "coordinate": [[896, 282], [957, 371]]}, {"idx": 7, "object": "bowl", "coordinate": [[359, 3], [602, 248]]}, {"idx": 8, "object": "bottle", "coordinate": [[943, 171], [1003, 277]]}, {"idx": 9, "object": "person", "coordinate": [[852, 498], [1188, 714]]}, {"idx": 10, "object": "bowl", "coordinate": [[579, 47], [798, 251]]}, {"idx": 11, "object": "laptop", "coordinate": [[42, 416], [627, 713]]}, {"idx": 12, "object": "carrot", "coordinate": [[915, 500], [1105, 579]]}, {"idx": 13, "object": "bottle", "coordinate": [[1003, 164], [1066, 272]]}, {"idx": 14, "object": "bottle", "coordinate": [[1040, 387], [1155, 512]]}, {"idx": 15, "object": "bottle", "coordinate": [[1079, 128], [1168, 242]]}, {"idx": 16, "object": "oven", "coordinate": [[17, 248], [1006, 711]]}, {"idx": 17, "object": "wine glass", "coordinate": [[4, 31], [353, 424]]}], "output": {"question index": 3, "question": "What is the position of the person relative to the bowl?", "options": {"A": "top right", "B": "bottom right", "C": "left", "D": "top left"}, "answer": "A"}}
{"input": [{"idx": 0, "object": "bottle", "coordinate": [[1154, 298], [1279, 471]]}, {"idx": 1, "object": "bottle", "coordinate": [[1109, 138], [1279, 405]]}, {"idx": 2, "object": "bottle", "coordinate": [[883, 101], [973, 320]]}, {"idx": 3, "object": "bottle", "coordinate": [[935, 232], [1038, 391]]}, {"idx": 4, "object": "bowl", "coordinate": [[491, 249], [730, 495]]}, {"idx": 5, "object": "bowl", "coordinate": [[711, 128], [903, 327]]}, {"idx": 6, "object": "bottle", "coordinate": [[896, 282], [957, 371]]}, {"idx": 7, "object": "bowl", "coordinate": [[359, 3], [602, 248]]}, {"idx": 8, "object": "bottle", "coordinate": [[943, 171], [1003, 277]]}, {"idx": 9, "object": "person", "coordinate": [[852, 498], [1188, 714]]}, {"idx": 10, "object": "bowl", "coordinate": [[579, 47], [798, 251]]}, {"idx": 11, "object": "laptop", "coordinate": [[42, 416], [627, 713]]}, {"idx": 12, "object": "carrot", "coordinate": [[915, 500], [1105, 579]]}, {"idx": 13, "object": "bottle", "coordinate": [[1003, 164], [1066, 272]]}, {"idx": 14, "object": "bottle", "coordinate": [[1040, 387], [1155, 512]]}, {"idx": 15, "object": "bottle", "coordinate": [[1079, 128], [1168, 242]]}, {"idx": 16, "object": "oven", "coordinate": [[17, 248], [1006, 711]]}, {"idx": 17, "object": "wine glass", "coordinate": [[4, 31], [353, 424]]}], "output": {"question index": 4, "question": "How should the carrot move to obtain the bottle?", "options": {"A": "down", "B": "up", "C": "left", "D": "right"}, "answer": "D"}}
